{
    "id": "138ea855d5cf411ca7f10873a52c096b",
    "title": "Passive Verb Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The work …………………. by my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "completed",
                "has completed",
                "was completed",
                "had completed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8d8a866591024886bc53c6c7028a777e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The match ………………… by our team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may won",
                "may be won",
                "has won"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06cf90c611364082ab6a2bf13d128ce0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let the weak not …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "insulted",
                "be insulted",
                "is insulted",
                "has insulted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e5ac4940a8f47308fb324e84e99497d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient ……………………… by the nurse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is looking after",
                "is being looked after",
                "has been looking after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff11aff4133844969377e2c9ac31a4a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sparrows …………………… by the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were feeding",
                "were being fed",
                "have fed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9ed5cb7afae947df8a762d1e489fdc44"
        },
        {
            "question": "The enemy troupes ………………….. by our army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have defeated",
                "was defeating",
                "have been defeated",
                "has been defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c33a05ec21f84cf1bb4f4ba898640620"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… a chair by the officer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "offered",
                "have offered",
                "was offered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c71bca807c5c492da8755a3290c6c404"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… to disclose your sources of income.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are requesting",
                "have been requesting",
                "are requested"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "906cef18ebcb4e06b654208296d07566"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let the door …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "open",
                "be opening",
                "be opened"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7fdef0f559f54365945049d1a0d4dcf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let this rubbish …………………… .. away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has thrown",
                "is thrown",
                "be thrown"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8cb06f093aa6440895953aec0af62780"
        }
    ]
}